One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Piece
‫ون بيس‬
Wano Arc
‫آرك وانو‬
Void
‫الفراغ‬
This is the Grand Line's Gloom Island, the ruins of the Muggy Kingdom.
‫هنا الغراند لاين، على جزيرة كورايغانا حيث تقع أطلال مملكة شيكيارو‬
In the old castle near the lake of this fallen country,
‫على مقربة من بحيرة قصر هذه المملكة المنهارة‬
lives a certain man...
‫يجلس رجل مرتاح البال‬
Warlord of the Sea
‫شيتشيبوكاي‬
A Warlord of the Sea...
‫إنه أحد الشيتشيبوكاي‬
World's Greatest Swordsman
‫أقوى سيافي العالم‬
and the world's greatest swordsman.
‫ويُعد أقوى سيافي العالم، اسمه...‬
Master Moria...
‫موريا-ساما...‬
He's... alive...
‫إنه... حي‬
"Gecko Moria and His Zombie Army Attack"...
‫"يشن غيكو موريا هجومًا مع جيشه من الزومبي"‬
He's alive!
‫إنه حي‬
Master Moria is really alive!
‫موريا-ساما حي، إنه موريا-ساما حقًّا‬
Look! It's amazing! Master Moria is alive!
‫انظر، سعيدةٌ بأنّ موريا-ساما على قيد الحياة‬
Yes, I read it this morning.
‫أجل، قرأت الخبر في الصباح‬
And you didn't think to tell me, you jerk?! This is very important to me!
‫لماذا لم تخبرني أيها الأحمق؟‬
I don't care.
‫لا يهمني‬
You should! He's my captain!
‫لكنه يهمني، إنه قبطاني‬
I thought he died in the Summit War two years ago!
‫ظننت أنه مات في حرب القمة قبل عامين‬
I'm so relieved!
‫أنا سعيدة حقًّا‬
If Master Moria is alive, maybe Absalom and Hogback are with him!
‫بما أنّ موريا-ساما حي، فقد يكون أبسالوم وهوغباك معه أيضًا‬
I just have to see him now! Let's get a move on!
‫أريد رؤيته، سأرحل‬
Oh, yeah...
‫هذا صحيح...‬
He let me stay here for ages.
‫لقد سمح لي بالمكوث هنا مدّةً طويلة‬
Ever since Bartholomew Kuma interrupted my confrontation with
‫في خضم معركتنا مع طاقم قبعة القش في ثريلر بارك‬
the Straw Hats at Thriller Bark and sent me flying here.
‫قذفني بارثولوميو كوما فجأة إلى هنا‬
So it's already been two years...
‫أحقًّا مضى على ذلك أكثر من عامين؟‬
Moria is as tenacious as the zombies he commands.
‫موريا رجل بسبع أرواح، كالزومبي الذي يتحكم بهم‬
Huh? Are you making fun of Master Moria?!
‫أتسخر من موريا-ساما؟‬
You ungrateful jerk!
‫أيها الجاحد‬
I owe him nothing.
‫لا أدين له بشيء‬
You owe me!
‫ولكنك تدين لي‬
Do you know how many times I cooked for you?!
‫أتعلم كم مرة طهيت لك؟‬
I cooked more than you did.
‫طهيت أكثر منك‬
I helped with the farming, too!
‫ساعدتك في الزراعة أيضًا‬
I let you stay here.
‫سمحت لكِ بالعيش هنا‬
You're so annoying!
‫أنت وقح حقًّا‬
Fine!
‫لا يهم‬
I'm leaving!
‫سأرحل‬
As you wish.
‫كما تشائين‬
I'm glad nothing's keeping me tied here.
‫لا شيء يبقيني مقيدة هنا‬
Take care of yourself.
‫اعتني بنفسك‬
Now you're nice?!
‫ما ألطفك‬
Damn you! Don't spring those kind words on me!
‫تبًّا لك، لا تقل كلامًا لطيفًا فجأة‬
Thank you for everything!
‫شكرًا لك على كل شيء‬
Such a noisome woman.
‫يا لكِ من امرأة صاخبة‬
But...
‫لكن...‬
the timing of your departure is likely fortuitous.
‫أراه قرارًا حكيمًا مغادرة هذا المكان الآن‬
The Reverie at Mary Geoise is currently underway...
‫في مؤتمر ليفيلي الذي عُقد في ماريجوا‬
during which an odd topic has arisen.
‫طُرح موضوع غريب على طاولة النقاش‬
The New World Pirate Island Beehive
‫العالم الجديد‬ ‫جزيرة القراصنة‬ ‫هاتشينوس‬ ‫هاتشينوس تأتي بمعنى خلية نحل أو خرق شخص بوابل من الرصاص‬
Charge!
‫عليكم بهم‬
Where's Absalom?!
‫أين أبسالوم؟‬
Where are you hiding him?!
‫أين أخفيتموه؟‬
Captain of the Thriller Bark Pirates (Former Warlord)
‫قبطان قراصنة ثريلر بارك‬ ‫(شيتشيبوكاي سابق)‬
Bounty: ¬320,000,000
‫المكافأة: 320 مليون بيري‬
Why can't I kill them?!
‫لماذا لا أستطيع قتلهم؟‬
Where's Absalom?!
‫أين أبسالوم؟‬
I don't know!
‫لا أعلم‬
None of you grunts know a damn thing!
‫أنتم الأتباع دائمًا لا تعرفون شيئًا‬
Where's Blackbeard?!
‫أين اللحية السوداء؟‬
Where is he?! Bring me Teach!
‫أين تيتش؟ استدعوا تيتش‬
Don't mess with us!
‫لا تعبث معنا‬
Didn't you hear what I said?!
‫ألم تسمعوني؟‬
I said, bring me Teach!
‫قلت لكم استدعوا تيتش‬
Teach! Where are you?!
‫تيتش، أين أنت؟‬
It's gotten noisy-meow.
‫يا للإزعاج-نيا‬
It's Gecko Moria, Captain Pizarro!
‫إنه غيكو موريا يا بيزارو-ساما‬
The former Warlord of the Sea!
‫إنه الشيتشيبوكاي السابق‬
Oh, why did you let him in?
‫لماذا سمحتم له بالدخول؟‬
H-He broke in! With his zombie army!
‫ا-اقتحم المكان بجيش مكوّن من الزومبي‬
The port is in ruins!
‫كما أنه دمّر الميناء‬
What does he want?
‫ما مراده؟‬
Fourth Captain of the Blackbeard Pirates
‫قبطان السفينة الرابعة في قراصنة اللحية السوداء‬
"Corrupt King"
‫الملك الفاسد‬ ‫أفالو بيزارو‬
He wants to see Commodore Teach!
‫يريد مقابلة العميد تيتش‬
Seems like he's looking for Absalom, the invisible man that came here recently.
‫يبدو أنه يبحث عن الرجل الخفي أبسالوم الذي أتى هنا قبل أيام‬
Oh, him!
‫عرفته‬
If you're not coming out,
‫إن لم تخرج...‬
I'm gonna bust in!
‫فسأدخل عنوة‬
Master Moria!
‫موريا-ساما‬
I'm here!
‫أنا هنا‬
Is that you, Absalom?!
‫أهذا أنت يا أبسالوم؟‬
Boss! It's me!
‫هذا أنا يا زعيم‬
Thank goodness! You're alive!
‫هذا مطمئن، أنت على قيد الحياة‬
I'm as good as new!
‫إنني حيٌّ أرزق‬
We didn't hear from you after we parted ways,
‫لم نسمع خبرًا منك منذ افتراقنا‬
so we got worried!
‫لذا قلقنا عليك‬
I'm sorry, Boss! It's just that this island is a paradise!
‫أعتذر يا زعيم، فهذه الجزيرة كالجنة‬
I was having so much fun that I forgot to keep in touch!
‫استمتعتُ بملذّاتها ونسيت التواصل معك‬
Well, that sounds like reason enough for me!
‫يسعدني أنّ هذا سبب عدم تواصلك معنا‬
But...
‫إذًا...‬
it looks like I went a little overboard...
‫لم يكن يجدر بي فعل هذا لهؤلاء المساكين‬
Zombies, that's enough!
‫هذا يكفي أيها الزومبي‬
Go back to the ship!
‫عودوا إلى السفينة‬
The Blackbeard Pirates are known for hunting people with abilities!
‫عُرف طاقم قراصنة اللحية السوداء بسرقتهم لقدرات فواكه الشيطان‬
That's right.
‫معك حق‬
The powers of your Clear-Clear Fruit are very desirable...
‫وأنت تملك قدرة على الاختفاء بفضل فاكهة الشفافية‬
since it allows you to become invisible.
‫الكثير يطمح بها‬
I know that, too...
‫أعرف ذلك‬
very well...
‫أعرفه حق المعرفة‬
What the...?!
‫ما هذا؟‬
Ouch! Damn it!
‫مؤلم، سحقًا‬
Who did that?!
‫من هناك؟‬
Where are you?!
‫أين أنت؟‬
Do you know who I am?
‫هل تعرفني؟‬
Shiryu... of the Rain!
‫شيريو المطر‬
You're that Impel Down dog that defected to Teach!
‫انضممت إلى تيتش بعدما كنت تعمل في إمبل داون‬
You got the gist of it.
‫أنت لست مخطئًا‬
Second Captain of the Blackbeard Pirates
‫قبطان السفينة الثانية في قراصنة اللحية السوداء‬
of the Rain
‫شيريو المطر‬
Do you like my power?
‫ما رأيك بقدرتي؟‬
You were invisible!
‫ألم تختفِ توًّا؟‬
That power belongs to Absalom...
‫تلك قدرة أبسالوم...‬
No way...!
‫أيعقل أنك...‬
Your suspicion is warranted, Gecko Moria.
‫حدسك صحيح يا غيكو موريا‬
The Invisible Man, Clear-Clear Fruit
‫بشري خفي بقدرة الشفافية‬
I've acquired a useful ability.
‫استوليت على قدرة مفيدة‬
Damn...
‫سحقًا...‬
Dammit!
‫سحقًا‬
Then, who the hell are you?!
‫أذًا فمن أنت أيها الوغد؟‬
Devon!
‫ديفون‬
Sixth Captain of the Blackbeard Pirates Dog-Dog Fruit, Model: Nine-Tailed Fox (Mythical Type)
‫قبطانة السفينة السادسة في قراصنة اللحية السوداء‬ ‫فاكهة الكلب، نوع: الثعلب ذو الذيول التسعة (زون أسطوري)‬
"Maiden Hunter"
‫صائدة الهلال‬ ‫كاترينا ديفون‬
– Captain Devon!
‫ديفون-ساما‬
Don't tell me Absalom is...
‫لا تخبراني بأنّ أبسالوم...‬
He shouldn't have come here so recklessly!
‫ما كان عليه التهور بالمجيء إلى هنا‬
We still have his body if you want it.
‫ما زلنا نحتفظ بجثته، أتريد العودة بها؟‬
You're fond of corpses, right?
‫فأنت تعشق الجثث، صحيح؟‬
Damn you guys! I won't forgive you!
‫لن أغفر لكم يا أوغاد‬
How dare you kill my friend?!
‫كيف تجرؤون على قتل رفيقي؟‬
I'll turn you all into corpses!
‫سأحولكم جميعًا إلى جثثٍ هامدة‬
Oh, I'd like to see you try.
‫عجبًا، أودّ أن أراك تحاول‬
Don't disturb the peace here on Pirate Island!
‫إياك إفساد سلام جزيرة القراصنة هذه‬
That voice...!
‫هذا الصوت...‬
Screw you! Show yourself!
‫كفاك هراءً، أظهر نفسك حالًا‬
No way!
‫لن أفعل‬
I'm relaxing now.
‫فأنا مسترخٍ الآن‬
This is a paradise for pirates!
‫هذه الجزيرة جنة للقراصنة‬
It oughta be fun!
‫لا غاية من دخولها سوى الاستمتاع‬
You guys!
‫يا رجال‬
Do you like to party?!
‫أتحبون الحفلات؟‬
If so,
‫إذًا...‬
come aboard my ship!
‫اصعدوا على متن سفينتي‬
Commodore of the Blackbeard Pirates & Emperor
‫أحد الأباطرة الأربعة - عميد قراصنة اللحية السوداء‬
Bounty: ¬2,247,600,000
‫المكافأة: 2 مليار و247 مليون و600 ألف بيري‬
Moria!
‫موريا‬
Don't you like...
‫ألا تحب...‬
to party?!
‫الحفلات أيضًا؟‬
Did you read the morning paper?
‫هل قرأت صحيفة اليوم؟‬
There's never a dull moment!
‫ليست مملة كالعادة‬
On the fourth day of the Reverie...
‫ففي اليوم الرابع من مؤتمر ليفيلي...‬
the commanders of the Revolutionary Army...
‫قادة الجيش الثوري...‬
burst into the Sacred Mary Geoise to take back Kuma,
‫اقتحموا ماريجوا لاستعادة كوما...‬
Meanwhile...
‫وفي مكانٍ آخر حاليًّا...‬
in Wano where the monstrous Kaido resides...
‫حيث يقطن الوحش كايدو في بلاد وانو‬
the arrival of Straw Hat...
‫وصل قبعة القش إليها‬
and a bunch of other hot-blooded punks has made headlines.
‫في ظل وجود حفنة من القراصنة الناشئين أمثاله‬
And chasing them is...
‫وتطاردهم...‬
the mad Emperor Big Mom!
‫الإمبراطورة الغاضبة بيغ مام‬
What do you think will happen?!
‫ما الذي سيحدث برأيك؟‬
It's already begun.
‫لقد بدأت سلفًا‬
In order to sit on the throne...
‫معركة حامية بين الأقوياء...‬
the mighty will crush one another!
‫للسيادة على العرش‬
Wano Act 2
‫الفصل الثاني من وانو‬
Mount Atama, Kuri, Wano
‫جبل أتاما في كوري‬ ‫وانو‬
He's as strong as Duke Inuarashi!
‫إنه يقاتل إينواراشي-ساما بكفاءة‬
That he can give Duke Inuarashi a run for his money... How impressive...
‫إينواراشي-ساما يعاني في مواجهته، مدهش‬
Why, Ashura?
‫لماذا يا أشورا؟‬
Why not use that tremendous power for Kuri, for Lord Oden's beloved people?!
‫لماذا لا تستغل كل هذه القوة في نصرة شعب مقاطعة كوري الذي أحبهم أودين-ساما؟‬
He's dead!
‫لأنه مات‬
Why did you guys even bother coming back after all this time?!
‫لماذا عدتم بعد كل تلك السنوات؟‬
We came back to fulfill Lord Oden's dream!
‫عدنا لتحقيق رغبة أودين-ساما‬
But you-gara have forgotten what happened to Lord Oden
‫لكن يبدو أنك نسيت ما حدث لأودين-ساما وغدوت تشهر سيفك إشباعًا لرغباتك الشخصية‬
Shut up!
‫اخرس‬
Don't talk as if you know everything!
‫لا تتحدث وكأنك تعرف كل شيء‬
If there is something you want to say, then say it!
‫إن كان لديك ما تقوله، تحدث‬
Foxfire Style: Fire-Willow Flash!
‫كيتسونيبي ريو كاريو إيسن‬ ‫أسلوب ثعلب النار: النيران الوامضة‬
Gentlemen...
‫يا رفاق...‬
That's enough.
‫كفاكما قتالًا‬
Inuarashi!
‫إينواراشي‬
Ashura!
‫أشورا‬
I thought you were better than this, Ashura!
‫لا تخذلنا يا أشورا-سان‬
Kiku!
‫كيكو‬
I've watched Wano since Lord Oden died two decades ago.
‫شهدتُ أوضاع بلاد وانو لعشرين سنة بعد موت أودين-ساما‬
You all think you can show up now and preach to me?
‫ثم تعودون فجأة طامحين بتحقيق شيء بعيد المنال؟‬
I won't listen!
‫لن أصغي إليكم‬
You should be thankful I'm not robbing you blind before I go!
‫كونوا شاكرين لأني لم أسلبكم ممتلكاتكم قبل أن أمضي‬
Don't you remember?!
‫هل نسيتم؟‬
This is how we were even back then!
‫هذه ماهيتي في الأيام الخوالي‬
I was fascinated by that man, Kozuki Oden.
‫كنتُ مخلصًا لرجل واحد، ألا وهو كوزكي أودين‬
I risked my life for him as a samurai!
‫خاطرت بحياتي من أجله بصفتي ساموراي تابعًا له‬
But I never pledged to support the rest of the Kozuki clan!
‫لكنني لم أقسم أبدًا بدعم بقية عشيرة الكوزكي‬
Right...
‫أليس كذلك...‬
Momonosuke?
‫يا مومونوسكي؟‬
Then I suggest you remember the kind of man that I was!
‫أنسيت أيُّ الرجال أكون؟‬
I won't give up!
‫أنا لن أستسلم‬
I'll have you join us!
‫سأضمّك إلى صفوفنا‬
Don't assume that everyone will be thrilled to see the return of the Kozuki Clan's samurai!
‫لا تظن بأنّ خبر عودة ساموراي عشيرة الكوزكي...‬
You guys abandoned the country for twenty years!
‫لقد هجرتم البلاد لعشرين سنة‬
You will never make up for that lost time!
‫لن تستطيعوا ملء الفراغ الذي خلفتموه‬
Are you hurt?
‫هل أنت بخير؟‬
No.
‫أجل‬
Let's go.
‫لنذهب‬
I am sorry to interrupt you.
‫أعتذر لمقاطعتكم‬
Raizo...!
‫رايزو-سان‬
I was able to locate Sir Luffy.
‫تمكنت من تحديد موقع لوفي-دونو‬
He is at the prisoner mining camp in Udon.
‫إنه في منجم السجناء في مقاطعة أودون‬
I thought so! Then, I am counting on you to handle it.
‫كما توقعت، أعتمد عليك في إخلاء سبيله‬
Understood!
‫عُلم‬
Otama! Are you awake?!
‫أوتاما، هل استيقظتِ؟‬
Master, what happened to me?
‫معلمي، ماذا حدث لي؟‬
You were attacked by Kaido, but these people treated you!
‫عالجكِ هؤلاء بعدما هاجمكِ كايدو وأحضروكِ إلى هنا‬
Oh, I see.
‫هكذا إذًا‬
Thank you!
‫شكرًا لكم‬
I am grateful!
‫ممتن لكم‬
Your injuries were minor. You'll get better soon!
‫إصاباتكِ بسيطة، ستتحسنين قريبًا‬
Thanks!
‫شكرًا‬
I was so scared, I just passed out.
‫أُغمي عليّ فورًا من شدة الخوف‬
I don't really remember the attack.
‫لذا لا أتذكر تفاصيل ما حدث بالضبط‬
I kinda remember Horsella fighting real hard...
‫كل ما أتذكره أنّ أومامي-تشان كانت تقاتل باستماتة‬
Where to, Master?!
‫إلى أين تريدين الذهاب يا سيدتي؟‬
An enemy became that loyal to you?
‫هل أصبحت تلك العدوة مخلصةً لك؟‬
What an astonishing power!
‫يا لها من قدرة مذهلة‬
What happened to Horsella and Big Bro?! Are they okay?!
‫أين أومامي-تشان وأخي الكبير؟ هل هما بخير؟‬
We don't know what happened to Horsella...
‫نجهل ما حلّ بالمدعوة أومامي‬
But Luffy was...
‫لكن لوفي...‬
Big Bro was pretty badly hurt...
‫تعرّض أخي الكبير لإصابات بليغة...‬
and taken to the mine in Udon?!
‫وأخذوه إلى منجم السجناء في أودون؟‬
Oh no!
‫مصيبة‬
Hey, you're wounded!
‫اهدئي، أنتِ مصابة‬
I'm more worried about Big Bro Luffy than my wounds!
‫إنني قلقة على أخي الكبير لوفي أكثر من إصاباتي‬
He'll be fine! Luffy's our captain!
‫لا تقلقي، فلوفي هو قبطاننا‬
Udon is a region of Wano.
‫تُعد أودون إحدى مقاطعات بلاد وانو‬
These days, it is mostly known for the prisoner mining camp.
‫لكنها باتت مركزًا لمصانع الأسلحة والمناجم‬
Udon, Wano
‫أودون‬ ‫ببلاد وانو‬
It's a dreadful place where serious offenders
‫إنه مكان مروّع يُجبر فيه أخطر المجرمين بتأدية الأعمال الشاقة حتى الموت‬
No one has ever escaped.
‫ولم يشهد أي حالات هروب منه قط‬
No, we don't need any geisha.
‫لا داعي لاستدعاء غيشا‬
Don't let anyone near this room!
‫لا تدع أي أحد أن يقترب من الغرفة‬
Yes, sir!
‫حاضر‬
You're bad...!
‫يا لك من ماكر‬
Here's the order for armor and weapons.
‫هذا طلب شحن الأسلحة الذي وردنا‬
Huh? Am I?
‫حقًّا؟‬
Oh, this is a lot! Is there going to be a war or something?
‫طلبوا الكثير، هل ستندلع حرب أو ما شابه؟‬
We don't know what's happening abroad.
‫نجهل ما يحدث خارج البلاد‬
We just make whatever they want.
‫نحن نصنع ما يطلبون من أسلحة فقط‬
You're so, so bad!
‫يا لك من ماكر‬
Huh? Am I?
‫حقًّا؟‬
Look closely, Onami. My old eyes can't handle this.
‫أمعني النظر يا أونامي، فقد ضعف بصري بسبب عمري‬
You're doing great! Keep calm while you watch.
‫لا تقلقي، راقبي بهدوء فحسب‬
His head is blocking my view.
‫رأس ذلك الرجل يحجب رؤيتي‬
Somebody's there!
‫من في العليّة؟‬
Who is it?!
‫من هناك؟‬
Who are they?!
‫من يكون؟‬
Search the attic!
‫اصعدوا إلى العليّة أيضًا‬
Catch them at any cost!
‫أمسكوه مهما كلف الثمن‬
Calm down, Shinobu!
‫اهدئي يا شينوبو-تشان‬
You're not getting away!
‫لن تهرب‬
Be quiet!
‫اهدئي‬
Where did they go?!
‫أين ذهب؟‬
Oh, is it just a cat?
‫أهي محض قطة؟‬
What's the matter with you, Shinobu?!
‫ما خطبك يا شينوبو-تشان؟‬
Are you okay?
‫هل أنتِ بخير؟‬
Onami...
‫أونامي...‬
there's something I haven't told you.
‫ثمة أمر لم أخبرك به...‬
Find them! Catch them!
‫ابحثوا عنه، اقبضوا عليه‬
Don't let the intruders get away!
‫إياكم السماح للدخيل بالهرب‬
I'm...
‫أنا...‬
afraid of sharp objects!
‫أخشى الأسلحة الحادة‬
You're not cut out for any kind of fight then!
‫لستِ مناسبة للقتال أبدًا‬
But Onami...
‫ولكن يا أونامي‬
a mature woman...
‫المرأة الناضجة...‬
is a deadly...
‫سلاح...‬
weapon.
‫مميت‬
Let's catch this wind.
‫لنمتطِ هذه الرياح‬
Ninpo: Great Kite!
‫نينبو أوداكو‬ ‫فنون النينجا: الطائرة الورقية‬
Great Kite
‫الطائرة الورقية‬
NIN
‫نينجا‬
Shinobu, this is amazing!
‫أنتِ مذهلة يا شينوبو-تشان‬
Haven't you found them yet?!
‫ألم تعثروا عليه بعد؟‬
What did you see in the residence, Onami?
‫ماذا رأيتِ في تلك الغرفة يا أونامي؟‬
Um...
‫رأيت...‬
Oh! I saw the name of the port and the shipment day!
‫رأيت اسم الميناء وتاريخ الشحنة‬
Well done!
‫أحسنتِ‬
Now we know when and where their weapons will arrive...
‫صرنا نعرف مكان وموعد وصول أسلحتهم‬
so we can steal them!
‫لنسرقهم‬
Look! Something's happening in town.
‫عجبًا، ثمة صخب في البلدة‬
What's that line for?
‫ما هذا الطابور؟‬
Is it a sale?!
‫تخفيضات؟‬
There are so many young ladies.
‫ثمة فتيات يافعات كُثُر‬
Welcome! Welcome!
‫أهلًا أهلًا بكن‬
Ladies, step right up and have a bite!
‫اقتربن وجربن يا آنسات‬
And of course that voice belongs to...
‫هذا الصوت، أيعقل...‬
It's sweet when it melts in your mouth.
‫ما ألذه حين يذوب في أفواهكن‬
That's al dente for you.
‫طهوتها على نارٍ هادئة‬
Sangoro's...
‫إنها من يدي سانغورو‬ ‫سانغورو = مكون من الرقمين 3 و5‬
nihachi soba!
‫نيهاتشي سوبا‬ ‫نيهاتشي = مكونة من الرقمين 2 و8‬
SANGORO'S NIHACHI SOBA
‫نيهاتشي سوبا = شعيرية دقيقة تصنع من دقيق الحنطة السوداء‬
Three, five, two, eight!
‫ثلاثة، خمسة، اثنان، ثمانية‬ ‫سانغونيهاتشي‬
The sum is the special number eighteen!
‫الرقم 18 يأتي بمعنى "مميز"‬
222233333
333332222
Special Soba
‫أوهاكو سوبا المميزة‬
It's my special soba!
‫إنها أوهاكو سوبا المميزة‬ ‫أوهاكو = 18‬
The noodles shine!
‫المعكرونة تلمع‬
They're so chewy!
‫وسهلة المضغ‬
– It's delicious!
‫لذيذة‬
Recruit some samurai already!
‫إنه لا يجمع الساموراي‬
Thank you!
‫شكرًا لكن‬
Troubling news!
‫خبرٌ عاجل‬
Ghosts are appearing to curse us!
‫ظهرت الأشباح مجددًا‬
Ghost sightings at the northern graveyard! Here's an update!
‫آخر المستجدات عن الأشباح التي شوهدت في المقبرة الشمالية‬
Oh? What's happening here?
‫ما الذي يحدث؟‬
I'll take a look.
‫سألقي نظرة‬
WANTED! Kamazo "the Reaper"
‫مطلوب!‬ ‫كامازو السفاح‬
Kamazo "the Reaper"?
‫كامازو السفاح؟‬
It's him!
‫ها قد ظهر‬
If you see him, that means you're already dead! How blood-chilling!
‫بمجرد رؤيته، ستكون عرضةً للموت‬
Who is he really?!
‫ما هويته الحقيقية؟‬
WANTED! Kamazo "the Reaper"
‫مطلوب!‬ ‫كامازو السفاح‬
My husband was killed by him, too!
‫قتل زوجي أيضًا‬
Now, gather 'round! Gather 'round!
‫هيا تجمعوا، تجمعوا‬
There's also news about the Witching Hour Boy, who appears at the third hour after midnight!
‫التالي هو فتى ساعة السحر الذي يظهر في ساعة السحر‬ ‫ساعة السحر تكون قبيل بزوغ الفجر يعتقد اليابانيين ظهور الأرواح والأشباح والشياطين خلالها‬
He's a thief who steals from the rich...
‫إنه لص بارع يسرق المال من الأغنياء ويعطيه الفقراء‬
Is he a hero or a villain?!
‫أهو حليف أم شرير؟‬
What is his true identity?!
‫ما هويته الحقيقية؟‬
If you want to know, buy a notice paper!
‫أتريدون المعرفة؟ اشتروا نسخة‬
Ah! Sir Witching Hour!
‫أوشيميتسو-ساما‬
I'll take one!
‫أعطني نسخة‬
Yes, thank you!
‫حاضر، تفضلي‬
Come and get your own!
‫هيا اشتروا نسخة‬
This notice paper is filled with exclusives!
‫إنه سبق صحفي‬
I'll take one, too!
‫سأشتري نسخة‬
Me, too!
‫وأنا أيضًا‬
The reversed crescent moon!
‫الهلال المعكوس‬
Who gave me this?
‫من أعطاني إياها؟‬
Are they really back?!
‫هل عادوا حقًّا؟‬
– The Kozuki Clan!
‫عشيرة الكوزكي‬
Hey, this could be the work of those ghosts.
‫مهلًا، أليس هذا من صنيع الأشباح؟‬
Suspicion will get us nowhere! This will spark a great fire!
‫لا داعي للشك، إنها شرارة ثورتنا‬
I'm going!
‫سأذهب‬
If this were ten years ago, I would have fought...
‫لو كان هذا قبل 10 سنوات، لقاتلت في صفهم‬
But what are you all going to do for weapons?
‫ولكن كيف ستحصلان على الأسلحة؟‬
This country prohibits all but samurai from carrying weapons.
‫لا يسمح سوى للساموراي بحمل السيوف في البلاد‬
All the kendo halls have closed down.
‫جميع قاعات المسايفة أُغلقت‬
Martial arts like karate and judo are also prohibited.
‫وجميع الفنون القتالية مثل الكاراتيه والجودو حُظرت‬
Orochi has already stamped out the spark of rebellion.
‫أوروتشي اتخذ سلفًا خطوات لقمع التمرد‬
I'll fight even if it's with my bare hands!
‫لا يهمني حتى إن قاتلت بيدي العاريتين‬
This will be our last chance! I've been waiting for so long!
‫إنها فرصتنا الأخيرة، لن أفرّط بها‬
I can't stop...
‫جسدي...‬
trembling with excitement!
‫يرتعش حماسة‬
Udon Prison Mine Wano
‫منجم السجناء في أودون‬ ‫ببلاد وانو‬
Sir Luffy.
‫لوفي-دونو‬
Raizo!
‫رايزو‬
Not so loud!
‫اخفض صوتك‬
What's wrong?
‫هل حدثت مشكلة؟‬
Nothing. I actually have good news.
‫لا، لدي أخبار سارّة‬
Otama is better.
‫تحسّنت حالة أوتاما‬
Okay, I'll be back later.
‫سأقابلك لاحقًا‬
Okay.
‫حسنًا‬
Hey, Jack...
‫يا جاك‬
the revenue from Kuri is pathetic.
‫الأرباح من مقاطعة كوري منخفضة للغاية‬
Now that Doflamingo's not around...
‫بعد خروج دوفلامينغو من تجارتنا‬
you know who our next business partner is, don't you?!
‫أنت تعرف من سيكون شريكنا التالي، صحيح؟‬
I'm sorry, Brothers...
‫أعتذر يا أخواي الكبيران‬
We don't need more deadweight than this idiot Queen.
‫لا نريد عبئًا‬
That's right! You don't need more scum when you've got King.
‫صحيح، يكفينا عبء مثل الحثالة كينغ‬
Queen "the Plague" Superstar Beast Pirates King "the Wildfire" Beast Pirates
‫كينغ الحريق‬ ‫نجم بارز في قراصنة الوحوش كوين الطاعون‬ ‫نجم بارز في قراصنة الوحوش‬
– Got that, Jack the stooge?!
‫هل فهمت يا جاك الفاشل؟‬
And you, Queen!
‫وأنت يا كوين‬
Why is it taking so long to break those brats?!
‫لماذا تأخذ كل هذا الوقت لكسر روح قرصانيْن صعلوكيْن؟‬
You no-account bum!
‫أنت غير كفء‬
Shut it, you sadistic pervert!
‫اخرس أيها السادي الحقير المنحرف‬